export const NQ_Data = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: `What is the Capital Of India ?`,
    options: [`New Delhi`, `Mumbai`, `Kolkatta`],
    answer: `New Delhi`
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: `Who is the CEO of Tesla Motors?`,
    options: [`Bill Gates`, `Steve Jobs`, `Elon Musk`],
    answer: `Elon Musk`
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: `Name World's Richest Man?`,
    options: [`Jeff Bezo`, `Bill Gates`, `Mark Zuckerberg`],
    answer: `Jeff Bezo`
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: `World's Longest River?`,
    options: [`River Nile`, `River Amazon`, `River Godavari`],
    answer: `River Nile`
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: `The next number in the sequence <b>1, 3, 6, 10,</b> is:`,
    options: [`13`, `15`, `16`],
    answer: `15`
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: `What is 55 in Roman Numerals ?`,
    options: [`XXXXXV`, `VC`, `LV`],
    answer: `LV`
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: `What colour do you get by mixing blue and yellow ?`,
    options: [`Brown`, `Green`, `Grey`],
    answer: `Green`
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: `What is the capital of Switzerland ?`,
    options: [`Berne`, `Geneva`, `Zurich`],
    answer: `Berne`
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: `If you sufffer from xenophobia, what are you afraid of ?`,
    options: [`Xylophones`, `Foreigners`, `Xanax's medicine`],
    answer: `Berne`
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: `In what year did the Berlin Wall come down?`,
    options: [`1976`, `1984`, `1989`],
    answer: `1989`
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: `What is the heaviest?`,
    options: [`Gold`, `Mercury`, `Platinium`],
    answer: `Platinium`
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: `Wich is the biggest state in the USA?`,
    options: [`California`, `Texas`, `Alaska`],
    answer: `Alaska`
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: `What is the largest man made structure on Earth?`,
    options: [`The Hadrian's Wall`, `The Great Wall of China`, `The Empire State Building`],
    answer: `The Great Wall of China`
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: `Wich sport is called "the sport of kings"?`,
    options: [`Archery`, `Hunting`, `Horse Riding`],
    answer: `Horse Riding`
  },
];
